{"items": [{"question": "additional benefit", "answer": "bonus", "options": ["bonus", "benignancy", "benign", "benignant"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Pleasant and beneficial", "answer": "benign", "options": ["benevolent", "benignancy", "benign", "benignant"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "not dangerous to health", "answer": "benignant", "options": ["benediction", "benignancy", "benevolent", "benignant"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The quality of being kind and gentle", "answer": "benignancy", "options": ["benevolent", "benignancy", "beneficent", "benediction"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "showing kindness", "answer": "benevolent", "options": ["benediction", "beneficent", "benevolent", "benefactor"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "praying for divine protection", "answer": "benediction", "options": ["beneficent", "beneficiary", "benediction", "benefactor"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Generous in assistance", "answer": "beneficent", "options": ["beneficiary", "benefit", "benefactor", "beneficent"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A person who helps people", "answer": "benefactor", "options": ["beneficiary", "benefit", "benefactor", "bona fied"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "The recipient of funds or other benefits", "answer": "beneficiary", "options": ["bona fied", "beneficiary", "fidelity", "benefit"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Financial assistance in time of need", "answer": "benefit", "options": ["benefit", "bona fied", "fidelity", "infidel"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Undertaken in good faith", "answer": "bona fied", "options": ["bona fied", "dictate", "infidel", "fidelity"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The quality of being faithful", "answer": "fidelity", "options": ["dictate", "dictator", "fidelity", "infidel"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A person who does not acknowledge your god", "answer": "infidel", "options": ["dictatorial", "infidel", "dictate", "dictator"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Issue commands or orders for", "answer": "dictate", "options": ["dictatorial", "dictator", "dictate", "predict"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A ruler who is unconstrained by law", "answer": "dictator", "options": ["dictatorial", "dictaphone", "predict", "dictator"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Characteristic of an absolute ruler or absolute rule", "answer": "dictatorial", "options": ["dictatorial", "contradict", "predict", "dictaphone"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "tell in\u00a0advance", "answer": "predict", "options": ["factory", "dictaphone", "predict", "contradict"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A tape recorder that records and reproduces dictation", "answer": "dictaphone", "options": ["fiction", "contradict", "dictaphone", "factory"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Be resistant to", "answer": "contradict", "options": ["manufacture", "contradict", "factory", "fiction"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A plant consisting of facilities for manufacturing", "answer": "factory", "options": ["fiction", "artificial", "manufacture", "factory"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The creation of something in the mind", "answer": "fiction", "options": ["manufacture", "clarity", "artificial", "fiction"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Make up something artificial or untrue", "answer": "manufacture", "options": ["simplify", "clarity", "artificial", "manufacture"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Contrived by art rather than nature", "answer": "artificial", "options": ["simplify", "liquefy", "clarity", "artificial"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Free from obscurity and easy to understand", "answer": "clarity", "options": ["clarity", "liquefy", "magnify", "simplify"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Make simpler or easier", "answer": "simplify", "options": ["voluntary", "simplify", "liquefy", "magnify"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Become liquid", "answer": "liquefy", "options": ["volition", "liquefy", "voluntary", "magnify"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "To enlarge beyond bounds or the truth", "answer": "magnify", "options": ["magnify", "voluntary", "volition", "placable"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Of your own free will or design", "answer": "voluntary", "options": ["placable", "voluntary", "placid", "volition"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A conscious choice or decision", "answer": "volition", "options": ["complacent", "placid", "placable", "volition"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Easily calmed or pacified", "answer": "placable", "options": ["placid", "donate", "complacent", "placable"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Not easily irritated", "answer": "placid", "options": ["placid", "complacent", "bonus", "donate"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "not looking to improve", "answer": "complacent", "options": ["donate", "bonus", "benign", "complacent"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Give to a charity or good cause", "answer": "donate", "options": ["bonus", "benignant", "benign", "donate"], "answer_index": 4}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 23.txt", "total": 33}